startpagepro.com 2007-12-24

# Privacy policy

#### ** Privacy Policy**

GoalSearch.com is committed to protecting your online privacy while providing you with the most useful and enjoyable Web experience possible.  You can use the features of GoalSearch.com anonymously.  However, there are some instances when we collect information. 

### **How we collect and use personal information**

If you enter a contest, respond to a promotion, or sign up for our newsletter, we may ask for your email address so we can notify contest winners and deliver promotional and content goodies. We occasionally may also send you e-mail to notify you about important changes to the site, new services, and special offers from us and select GoalSearch.com partners. If you would rather not receive such information, you can indicate this when you enter your e-mail address.

### **How we protect your personal information**

In addition to using the most secure technology available, we work tirelessly to make sure that we use any information you provide us only in ways you have approved. We send you only the e-mail you have approved in your account information or on your e-mail subscription sign-up page. 

### **How we use "cookies"**

As you probably know, "cookies" are small pieces of information that some Web sites store on your computer's hard drive when you visit them. Like many other Web sites, GoalSearch.com uses cookies to identify members for advertising purposes. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies but allow you to modify security settings so you can approve or reject cookies on a case-by-case basis. Even if you do not use cookies, you can still access all of the features on our site.

### **What we provide to third parties**

While GoalSearch.com does not provide any third-party access to your personal information, we may provide third parties with aggregate statistics about our customers, traffic patterns, and related site information. This data reflects site usage patterns gathered during thousands of customer visits to our Web site each month, but it does not contain behavioral or identifying information about any individual member unless that member has given us permission to share that information.

GoalSearch.com uses a third-party advertising company to serve ads when you visit our sites. This company may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address, or telephone number) about your visits to our and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. In addition, we collect statistical information via a third party.  For this purpose, we and our third-party statistics company places a  pixel tags (also called “clear gifs”). The advertising company does not collect any information that can identify you as an individual. 

### **Obtaining your consent**

By using our Web site, you give GoalSearch.com permission to collect information about the pages served to you as an anonymous user for the purpose of calculating aggregate site statistics. 

If you are under the age of 18, you must not provide your name, e-mail address, or any other identifying information without the consent of your parent or guardian, or as otherwise provided for by applicable law.

Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

### **Tell us what you think**

GoalSearch.com welcomes your questions and comments about our privacy policy. Please contact us [here](http://www.free-essays-term-papers.com/site/contact_us.htm).
